numbeo.com 2019-11-24

# Privacy Policy

Numbeo.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy to our customers and users of this website. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Numbeo.com uses, maintains and discloses information collected from its customers and users of its website.

**Information We Collect**  
Numbeo.com may request or collect personal information from online users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where users are invited to volunteer such information.

The data we collect is information that identifies you personally, and may include:  
\- Your name  
\- E-mail address  
\- Birthdate  
\- Security Question  
\- Postal address

Numbeo.com may also collect information about how users access the website using a tracking ID unique to each user through the use of cookies.

**What are Cookies?**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For session ID cookies, once you close your browser or log out, the cookie terminates and is erased. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on your computer’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Your browser’s help file contains information and instructions for removing persistent cookies. Session ID cookies may be used by Numbeo.com to track user preferences while the user is visiting the website. They also help to minimize load times and save on server processing. Persistent cookies may be used by Numbeo.com to store whether, for example, you want your password remembered or not, and other information. Cookies used on the Numbeo.com website do not contain personally identifiable information.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard websites, we use log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. However, none of the information stored in our log files, including but not limited to IP addresses, is linked to personally identifiable information.

**How we use this information**  
Numbeo.com may use the personally identifiable information collected by Numbeo.com to contact customers regarding products and services offered by Numbeo.com and, to the extent the user has agreed to it, by its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. We may also use this information for research purposes regarding the effectiveness of our website services, marketing, advertising and sales efforts. Except as outlined below, Numbeo.com will not in any way share this information with a third party unless you specifically authorize such disclosures. Numbeo.com does not sell or rent your contact information to third parties.

**Disclosure of Information**  
Numbeo.com may disclose your personal information as it deems necessary, in Numbeo.com‘s sole discretion, to: (a) comply with legal process or other legal requirements, including but not limited to responding to civil or criminal subpoenas, search warrants, national security letters, court orders, or other requests for information from law enforcement officials; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Numbeo.com or its officers, agents, affiliates, licensees, and customers; or (c) carry out its obligations under or enforce this Agreement or to assign its rights under this Agreement.

Numbeo.com may from time to time engage third parties, including its own subsidiaries and affiliated companies, to preserve, analyze or otherwise store or process data received by Numbeo.com from its customers. Such third party service providers are required to treat all such data with the same degree of care as Numbeo.com and are prohibited from disclosing such data to any other person or party, except as otherwise provided for in this Privacy Policy.

Numbeo.com RESERVES THE RIGHT (SUBJECT TO APPLICABLE LOCAL LAW), IN ITS SOLE DISCRETION, TO MONITOR YOUR ACCOUNT, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE USE OF A USER'S MAIN ACCOUNT AND ANY SUB-ACCOUNTS, FOR THE PURPOSE OF INVESTIGATING VIOLATIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT OR TO ASSIST WITH CRIMINAL OR CIVIL INVESTIGATIONS.

Numbeo.com may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from users to investors and potential partners. In such cases, only statistical information will be disclosed and personally identifiable data will be kept confidential. In case Numbeo.com is sold, the information collected from users may be transferred to the new owners.

**Special Offers and Updates**  
Our customers and users will occasionally receive newsletters or e-mails with information on products, services, or special offers. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, Numbeo.com gives them the opportunity to opt-out from receiving these types of communications.

**Service Announcements**  
On rare occasions, it is necessary to send out a strictly service-related announcement, if, for instance, our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
The Numbeo.com website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Numbeo.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The Numbeo.com Privacy Policy as described herein applies solely to information collected by Numbeo.com.

**Maintenance of Information**  
The information provided to Numbeo.com is saved indefinitely and may be stored on one or more databases directly or indirectly maintained by Numbeo.com. Numbeo.com employs industry-standard security measures to protect the confidentiality of the information. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur; we make every effort to prevent such occurrences.

**Your Responsibility**  
You are responsible for the security of your Customer ID and passwords. Make sure you keep them in a safe place and do not share them with others. Always remember to log out after your session ends to ensure that others cannot access your private personal information. You should take this precaution even if you are not using a public computer, such as at a library or internet café, but even when using your private computer in your home.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit [this URL](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

**How we secure personal information**  
We use standard Linux and MySQL security features to protect personally identifiable data. 

**Removing personally identifiable information**  
To remove personally identifiable information associated with your email address, please use this URL. To remove cookies, please check the documentation of your web browser. 

Privacy policy contact information:   

    Numbeo Doo
      Drziceva 9/13
      11120 Belgrade
      Serbia
      email: contact@numbeo.com
